And so, this number is canceled out and—
E, então, este número é anulado...
Teacher.
Professor, neste caso, não é mais eficiente usar esta fórmula?
My, Prince Cecil. No such theorem exists.
Ora, Príncipe Cecil, este teorema não existe.
Indeed. I've just created it.
Sim, eu acabei de criar.
Cecil 10 Years Old
Cecil - 10 anos
What? Your Highness is exceptional, but that isn't...
Hã? Mesmo sendo Vossa Alteza, isso é...
I-It works?!
Hã? Tá certo!
But that means this is a new discovery in the world of mathematics!
Então esta é uma nova descoberta da matemática!
By connecting the parts we were given, I believe it arises quite simply.
Se você juntar as partes do problema,
I-I'm going to go make a report to the society!
E-Eu vou ao conselho acadêmico para informá-los!
He's gone.
Ele se foi...
Well, it doesn't matter.
Bom, tudo bem.
When I can understand a thing after hearing it once,
Não acho produtivo ficar ouvindo a mesma coisa
I can't say that hearing it over a prolonged period of time is beneficial.
que eu entendi na primeira vez.
Prince Cecil!
Príncipe Cecil!
I am a villainess!
Eu sou a nobre vilã!
My role is to rip Your Highness and the heroine away from each other,
O meu papel é separar você e a heroína
and have you left in complete shock in the end!
para, no final, você me derrotar!
Chapter 1
Episódio 01
An Observation Log of Meeting a Self-Proclaimed Villainess.
O Registro do Encontro com
I am Cecil Glo Alphasta.
Sou Cecil Glo Alphasta.
I am the First Prince of the Kingdom of Alphasta and its crown prince.
Sou o primeiro príncipe, o herdeiro da coroa do Reino Alphasta.
Today is the day that my fiancée,
Hoje foi o meu primeiro encontro
Bertia Ibil Noches, daughter of a marquis,
com a minha noiva Bertia Ibil Noches, filha do marquês.
it seems that I'm not the only one who doesn't understand what she's saying.
Parece que não sou o único que não entendeu o que ela quis dizer.
Miss Bertia, standing and chatting isn't really the thing to do.
Senhorita Bertia, por que não nos sentamos para um chá e conversamos?
What?
Hã? Claro...
This is Zeno.
Ele é Zeno, meu servo particular.
Zeno
Zeno
Stare...
Encara...
Is something wrong?
Algum problema?
Prince Cecil, aren't you a little too composed for your age?
Alteza, não é comportado demais para alguém de sua idade?
Is it possible that you're a reincarnation?
Vai me dizer que é um reencarnado?
A reincarnation?
Reencarnado?
I was taught that this is how royals should behave themselves.
A realeza recebe educação para se comportar assim.
It's only natural.
É o esperado.
No, it isn't!
Mas é claro que não!
If there was some other detached,
Até parece que existe outro príncipe tão elucidado!
The voice inside your heart is spilling out, Zeno.
Seus pensamentos estão vazando, Zeno.
Well, then. Will you explain what you were saying before?
Então, poderia me explicar o que falou?
Of course!
Mas é claro!
I must have Your Highness understand everything
Quero que se torne uma pessoa digna de me rejeitar, já sabendo de tudo.
This may shock you, but I have memories of my past life.
Talvez se surpreenda,
In the land where I was born and raised, Japan,
Eu nasci e cresci em um país chamado Japão,
there were stories I could watch with moving pictures that were like novels.
e eu gostava de algo que era como um romance escrito, mas com desenhos que se movem.
Japan Woman A Playing a Game
Japão Garota A Jogando algo
Cecil Glo Alphasta
Cecil Glo Alphasta Ora, você veio.
These "otome games" were something I enjoyed immensely.
Também é conhecido como "otome game".
Hey, it's you.
Ora, você veio.
Then, when I regained my memories,
E quando eu recuperei minhas memórias, percebi.
That otome game had depicted this world.
Esse otome game mostrava este mundo.
That's why I know the whole scenario... the future.
Por isso, eu sei a história... sei o futuro.
Your Highness will fall in love with a noble's daughter, the Maiden of Destiny.
Vossa Alteza irá se apaixonar pela moça de seu destino,
I, the villainess, will turn into a jealous demon and torment her horribly.
então eu, como a vilã, irei morrer de ciúmes e maltratá-la.
This will enrage Your Highness.
Então Vossa Alteza irá se enfurecer, cancelar nosso noivado e acabar com minha família!
In short, getting the better of me allows the two of you to find happiness together!
Ou seja, eu serei totalmente derrotada e vocês serão felizes!
Though my fate is to fall, I will do it beautifully!
Mesmo que meu destino seja triste, terá que ser belo!
I will become a first-rate flower of evil!
Para isso, eu vou me tornar a melhor flor do mal!
Before this, I've never once been unable to understand what someone was saying.
Até hoje, nunca aconteceu de eu não entender uma palavra
Though, to be honest, whether she has an overactive imagination,
Bom, sinceramente, não me importo que ela tenha tendências à loucura
or the power to predict the future, it doesn't matter to me.
ou o poder de prever o futuro.
In short, she's aiming to become a person who fits into this scenario of hers.
O fato é que ela está almejando a pessoa dessa tal história.
As long as it isn't something problematic for a future queen, I don't mind at all.
Se isso não afetará sua aparência como rainha, tanto faz.
I was wondering, what exactly is this first-rate flower of evil you mentioned?
Aliás, o que seria essa "flor do mal de primeira" que disse?
Strong, noble, and beautiful!
Forte, sublime e bela!
Though her path may lead to destruction, she treads it without hesitation!
Serei assim sem dúvidas, mesmo que seja o caminho da destruição!
That's the kind of woman I'm talking about!
É uma mulher assim!
Strong, noble...
Forte, sublime e bela...
N-No, you have the wrong idea!
N-Não é isso!
Bertia was always supposed to be someone who didn't really have a chance.
A Bertia sempre foi uma personagem a ser sacrificada, então sua aparência é subjetiva.
She sounds like a sad sort of person.
Parece ser uma existência triste.
Are you all right with all of that?
Você está conformada com isso?
I am not all right.
N-Não estou.
Everything I spoke of was the Bertia in the game.
Essa é a história da Bertia no jogo...
I am... I am myself!
E eu... Eu sou eu.
In my past life, I tended to hide in my own shell, but you were my support.
Mas eu desejo a sua felicidade, Príncipe Cecil,
Prince Cecil, I wish for your happiness!
pois você era o suporte de alguém como eu, com tendências à reclusão.
And that is why I will become an honest, righteous flower of evil!
Por isso, eu...
An honest, righteous flower of evil?
Flor do mal pura e correta...
I will improve myself and come again!
Eu vou me aperfeiçoar e vir novamente!
A pleasant day to you!
Tenha um bom dia.
Bertia has run away
Bertia fugiu
I wonder what all that was.
O que foi isso?
Your Highness, what will you do?
Alteza, o que houve?
Well...
Pois é...
as far as becoming my fiancée,
Apesar de ser minha noiva,
she has none of the manners necessary to interact with royalty,
ela não tem a etiqueta adequada para lidar com a realeza,
and I don't understand many of her words and actions.
e tem muitas ações dela que não compreendo.
And that is exactly what makes her so entertaining.
Por isso mesmo ela é interessante.
I will observe her for a while.
Vou observá-la por um tempo.
If it becomes necessary, I need only tame—
Quando precisar, eu posso treiná-la...
lead her down the correct path.
Digo, posso orientá-la para o caminho correto.
You seem like you're enjoying yourself.
Parece estar se divertindo.
This sense of unpredictability isn't bad at all.
Essa sensação de imprevisibilidade é interessante.
Generally, if I try something, I can do it on my first attempt,
Para mim, que sempre consegui fazer tudo de primeira,
so, for me, the world is a tedious place.
o mundo é muito tedioso.
I've rarely ever felt a sense of accomplishment.
Eu quase nunca senti o que é a conquista.
In my eyes, the world has lost its color.
O mundo que vejo sempre esteve desbotado.
Which is why...
Por isso...
I hope you won't betray my expectations.
Não traia minhas expectativas, viu?
One Year Later
Um ano depois
Your Highness, there is a report from that messenger.
Alteza, relatório sobre o que pediu.
Lady Bertia has secluded herself within her home for a year.
Passou um ano desde que a Senhorita Bertia ficou reclusa.
Surely it's cause for concern now.
Dá para ficar preocupado.
I've been sending messengers to go and see how she's faring.
Eu fico pedindo para irem ver como está,
She's in exceedingly good spirits.
mas a Senhorita Bertia está bem.
Then why has she shut herself away?
Então por que ela está reclusa?
Zeno, you will understand once you see her.
Você vai entender quando vê-la.
She should make an appearance very soon.
Ela irá aparecer em breve.
A Few Days Later
Dias depois
It has been quite some time, Your Highness.
Há quanto tempo, príncipe!
You don't know who I am, you say?
Não sabe quem eu sou?
Bertia Ibil Noches!
Bertia Ibil Noches.
Your Highness's fiancée!
A sua noiva.
Well, this is something. Her appearance has changed quite a bit.
Olha só, sua aparência mudou bastante.
It seems that those reports were true.
Os relatos estavam corretos.
Just two more kilos!
Mais dois quilômetros!
Did you mistake me for someone else? You didn't recognize me, did you?
Você nem me reconheceu! Você nem me reconheceu, né?
Ow!
Ah!
What sort of attitude is that to take toward the crown prince, Bertia?
Que atitude é essa, perante o príncipe herdeiro?
What are you doing, Father?
O que raios tá fazendo, pai?
Your Highness, please forgive my idiot daughter's rudeness.
Vossa Alteza, perdoe a grosseria da minha filha.
Please, don't let it trouble you.
Não se preocupe. É uma atitude infantil e fofa, oras.
Y-Your Highness... would you please say that one more time?
Então... Vossa Alteza. Poderia repetir... por favor?
When you, um... said "adorable."
Bem... quer dizer, sobre ser fofa...
Bertia.
Bertia...
Don't let his appearance fool you. His Highness's eyes never smile, do they?
Não se deixe enganar pelas aparências.
He doesn't have the emotions necessary to dote on cute things. He's too cold.
É uma pessoa fria que não tem o menor sentimento de admiração por coisas fofas.
You will make do with my love-filled use of "adorable."
Contente-se com o meu amor carinhoso.
You're adorable!
Que fofa!
I wonder if the marquis is aware that what he said was ruder than Miss Bertia.
Será que o marquês tem consciência de que está sendo ainda mais indelicado do que a Srta. Bertia?
Oh, Kuro!
Ah, Kuro!
I knew it. It is alive, isn't it?
Então isso aí está vivo...
I'm terribly sorry.
Desculpe. Desde que o encontrei, ele não sai do meu lado...
So I had her imitate a scarf and brought her with me.
Eu o trouxe disfarçado de cachecol.
Imitate.
Disfarçado... mas não estava, na verdade.
I thought it must be so.
Eu sabia.
If I keep quiet about it now, it'll make things more entertaining in the future.
Vai ficar mais interessante, se eu ficar quieto.
Now, please have some sweets before the tea gets cold.
Vamos, aproveite os doces, enquanto o chá ainda está quente.
Thank you! I'll have some!
Sim! Vou comer!
Diet.
Dieta...
This cake was made with a reduced amount of sugar.
Esse bolo tem pouco açúcar, viu?
I'm not particularly good with sweets, you see?
É que eu não sou muito fã de doces.
Reduced sugar! Cake!
Baixo teor de açúcar! Bolo!
Please, have some.
Por favor, sirva-se!
I thought she was aiming to become a strong, noble flower of evil, wasn't she?
Ela não estava buscando se tornar uma flor do mal forte e nobre?
I feel like she's heading in the opposite direction.
Tenho a sensação de que estamos indo em direções totalmente opostas, mas...
Well, shall we begin speaking of tomorrow?
Bem, acho que já está na hora de falarmos sobre amanhã.
Yes! At the party tomorrow, as a first-rate villainess,
Sim! Na festa de amanhã,
I'll nobly fulfill my duty as Your Highness's partner!
como uma nobre vilã de primeira, vou desempenhar com dignidade o papel de parceira de Vossa Alteza!
Why is it, I wonder?
Por que será? Eu deveria sentir confiança, mas me sinto ansioso.
That's very reassuring.
Isso é reconfortante.
But the fact that you're a villainess and that you have memories of a past life...
Mas quanto à questão de ser uma vilã e às memórias da vida passada,
let's keep that a secret between just you and I.
vamos manter como um segredo só nosso.
Why?
Por quê?
Because the high society that we're about to enter into
O mundo social em que vamos nos expor
is a world where you never know what may end up having a harmful result.
é um mundo onde nunca se sabe o que pode vir a ser um obstáculo.
A flower of evil who leaves herself open to attack would seem inferior, no?
Uma “Flor do Mal” cheia de falhas parece bem inferior, não é?
I-I see!
Ah, entendi!
Defeating one's opponents in secret is first-rate,
Quem derruba os inimigos de forma sorrateira é de primeira.
while talking big and digging one's own grave is third-rate!
Quem fala demais e se expõe é de quinta categoria.
I completely understand!
Entendi!
I'm different from the Bertia in the game
Eu sou diferente da Bertia do jogo,
because I will become a beautiful, noble flower of evil!
afinal, vou me tornar uma Flor do Mal bela e nobre!
I'm so glad you understand.
Que bom que você entendeu.
Though I feel her understanding is slightly skewed.
Tenho impressão que não era bem isso...
Tomorrow is my eleventh birthday, and I'm happy to have you there celebrating it.
Estou muito feliz por poder comemorar meu aniversário de 11 anos com você amanhã.
I'm also happy that I will be celebrating Your Highness's...
Fico feliz por poder comemorar meu aniversário junto com—
Eleven?
11 anos? Vossa Alteza, vai fazer 11 anos?
That's right. You didn't know?
É, sim. Você não sabia?
No, I knew. It's just...
Não, eu já sabia.
Your Highness, my mother... my mother is going to die!
Alteza, minha mãe... Minha mãe... vai morrer!
Your mother?
Sua mãe?
According to the scenario,
No enredo, devido a uma doença contagiosa que começou a se espalhar no verão,
Just before my tenth birthday, my mother will die.
pouco antes do meu aniversário de 10 anos,
An epidemic?
Uma doença contagiosa?
Apparently, a certain infectious disease evolves.
Parece que uma certa doença contagiosa evoluiu.
It takes time to find a method to treat it, and on top of that,
Além de demorar para se encontrar um medicamento,
the herb needed for the medicine...
a erva medicinal para tal,
luona leaf, there won't be enough of it.
a erva Luona, ficará em falta.
A great many people will lose their lives.
Muitas pessoas perderão a vida.
Luona leaf.
A erva Luona...
It's definitely a medicinal plant that is difficult to cultivate.
De fato, é uma erva medicinal considerada difícil de cultivar, não é?
Father searches frantically for luona leaf, but he isn't able to obtain any.
Meu pai procura desesperadamente pela erva Luona, mas não consegue encontrá-la...
In the end, he asks His Majesty to spare him some, but...
No final, ele pede à Sua Majestade que nos conceda uma parte das reservas do Tesouro, mas...
What you're speaking of happens a year from now, doesn't it?
Você está falando do que vai acontecer daqui a um ano, não é?
If you prepare for it now, won't you be able to save your mother?
Se nos prepararmos agora, talvez possamos salvá-la, não é?
But, if I do that, the scenario will...
Mas... assim, a história irá...
The scenario or your mother? Which is more important?
O que é mais importante: a história ou a sua mãe?
Of course my mother is!
Claro que é a minha mãe!
But... but if the scenario gets twisted, Your Highness will...
Mas...
Me?
Eu?
Your Highness.
Vossa Alteza.
Here. Wipe your tears.
Vamos lá, enxugue as lágrimas.
I'm your fiancé.
Eu sou o seu noivo.
If you ever find yourself in trouble, let's think about what to do together.
Se tivermos algum problema, vamos pensar juntos no que fazer.
One Year Later
Um ano depois Mansão dos Noches
Your Highness is simply awful!
Vossa Alteza, isso é cruel demais!
Honestly! Honestly! Oh, honestly, honestly, honestly!
Caramba!
P-Please, forgive me. That behavior was unbecoming of a lady.
Desculpe.
No, I should be the one to apologize.
Não, eu que peço desculpa.
Have I done something to cause that charming face of yours to crumple?
Será que fiz algo para que distorcesse seu rosto lindo?
Today is already my tenth birthday!
Hoje já é o meu aniversário de 10 anos, ouviu?
I wanted to develop more of a strategy against the epidemic...
Eu queria ter tomado mais medidas contra a doença contagiosa...
but in your letters you only ever replied, "It's all right."
Nas cartas, você só responde dizendo que está tudo bem, e...
What was I supposed to do?
O que eu devo fazer?
I'm sorry.
Desculpa.
I didn't realize that you were feeling so distraught.
Eu não imaginei que você se sentisse tão encurralada.
But everything really is all right. That's why I wrote that in my letters.
Mas eu só escrevi na carta que está tudo bem, porque, de fato, está.
I desperately tried to collect luona leaf, but I don't have nearly enough.
Eu juntei toda erva Luona que pude, mas está longe de ser suficiente.
And for some reason, when summer came, the disease didn't spread.
Não sei por que a doença não se espalhou, sendo estamos no verão.
And my mother is in perfect health.
Minha mãe também está cheia de energia...
I just don't understand what's going on anymore!
Eu... já não sei mais o que está acontecendo!
Don't worry. The epidemic did begin, just as you said it would.
Tudo bem. Como você disse, a doença realmente se espalhou.
It's simply already died down.
É só que as coisas já se acalmaram.
So the infectious disease really did spread?
Então a doença se espalhou?
What?
O quê?
I used your information to guess the disease and made medicine for it.
Eu criei um remédio com base nas informações que você me deu para tratar a doença.
As soon as it began to spread, the patients received immediate treatment.
Tratamos os pacientes assim que a doença começou a se espalhar.
W-Wait, Your Highness! What do you mean?
Ei, espere aí, Alteza! O que está acontecendo?!
You're the only one allowed to treat me this way, Miss Bertia.
Você é a única pessoa capaz de fazer isso comigo Srta. Bertia.
I understand. First, let's calm down a little.
Já entendi, então vamos nos acalmar um pouco, tá?
How can I possibly stay calm? Hurry up and explain, please!
Como ficaria calma com isso?!
Let's take a little walk outside.
Vamos dar uma volta lá fora.
Now, let's go back to just after you spoke to me about your mother.
Então, vamos relembrar o que aconteceu depois que me falou da sua mãe.
His Majesty seemed to be very pleased.
Sua Majestade estava bem animado.
One Year Ago
Um ano atrás No palácio
He gave you permission to use the greenhouse right away.
Ele nos concedeu permissão para usar a estufa.
Perhaps, with the worry of what to get his son as a birthday present gone,
Acho que ficou aliviado porque não sabia o que dar
he felt relieved.
de presente de aniversário pro filho.
And what will you do next?
O que fará agora?
First, the library.
Primeiro, vamos à biblioteca.
I must look into luona leaf.
Preciso pesquisar sobre a erva Luona.
Some Time Later
Um tempo depois
It was so simple to successfully cultivate luona leaf.
Consegui cultivar a erva Luona sem grandes dificuldades...
A giant luona plant has grown.
Uma erva Luona enorme nasceu
Luona leaf grows this big? Was it Your Highness who grew this?
Como é que a erva Luona cresceu tanto?
Since I have this, maybe I'll try making some medicine.
Já que estou aqui, por que não tentar fazer o remédio?
To do that, I'll first have to identify the infectious disease.
Primeiro, preciso identificar a doença contagiosa.
I asked Miss Bertia about the characteristics of the disease...
Depois de ouvir a Srta. Bertia descrever a doença...
Asked Questions at Noches House
Colhendo informações com a Srta. Bertia
My mother's disease?
Sobre a doença da minha mãe?
I borrowed knowledge from experts in medicine and pharmacy...
E com base no conhecimento de especialista em medicina e ervas,
Asked Questions at the Royal Palace
Colhendo informações no palácio
and I was able to identify the disease.
consegui identificar a doença.
There's nothing left that I can teach you, Your Highness.
Não há mais nada que eu possa ensinar a Vossa Alteza.
It's likely that the disease is a mutation of this one.
Leu um monte de livros
Read a Mountain of Books.
Provavelmente, trata-se de uma mutação dessa doença contagiosa.
And so a remedy...
Fez alguns experimentos
Performed a Number of Experiments
E o medicamento...
Easily Completed.
Foi finalizado facilmente
I've gone and done it.
...acabou ficando pronto.
You made it quite easily, didn't you?
Você o criou sem muito esforço...
Well, we don't know if it's effective or not.
Bom, se funciona ou não,
There's no way to test it without someone stricken by the disease.
só poderei verificar quando alguém adoecer.
But if we truly want to be prepared, I'll have to make the adults take action.
No entanto, se for realmente me preparar...
I'll pretend that I just happened to take an interest in a certain disease,
Fingi ter demonstrado interesse por uma determinada doença contagiosa,
and invite a doctor who is studying it to the palace as my teacher.
convidei o médico que estudava essa matéria para a corte para ser meu mestre.
I'll passionately discuss infectious diseases.
Discutimos sobre doenças contagiosas.
I vehemently insist!
Blá blá blá intenso!
Then we'll discuss the possibility of a new strain and how to combat it.
Discutimos a possibilidade de isso se tornar uma nova doença e as medidas a serem tomadas...
I vehemently insist!
Blá blá blá intenso!
As a separate matter,
Além disso, aproveitei para falar sobre os benefícios da erva Luona, cujo cultivo eu estava curtindo.
A huge hint!
Grande dica!
and speak quite passionately.
Cecil deu uma grande dica.
Then, I set it up so that the new disease strain would connect to the luona leaf.
Então era só fazer com que a nova doença se relacionasse com a erva Luona.
If I can get him to come to the realization himself, then...
Se eu conseguisse fazer com que ele percebesse...
If it has such effects,
Quem diria que tinha esse efeito!
then it's likely to be useful in my colleague's research...
Isso deve ajudar na pesquisa de um conhecido,
I'll tell them about it.
então vou explicar para ele.
The effect was lackluster.
O efeito foi meia-boca
It's not in your colleague's research, but yours that it should prove useful.
Eu queria que isso fosse útil para sua pesquisa, não do amigo.
Why is he unable to realize something so simple?
Por que será que ele não consegue perceber algo tão simples assim?
Your Highness, you seem to be fighting a difficult battle.
Vossa Alteza, parece estar enfrentando dificuldades.
And you seem oddly happy, Zeno.
Você parece estar feliz, Zeno.
No, not especially.
Ah, não, de jeito nenhum!
Still, he is an excellent doctor.
Bem, mas ele também é um médico excelente. Ele vai acabar percebendo isso.
A Few Months Later
Meses depois
I vehemently insist!
Blá blá blá intenso!
wouldn't that luona leaf have some effect against the disease?
O médico teve a ideia
Perhaps it would.
Talvez essa erva ajude contra aquela doença.
That took a long time.
Demorou bastante, hein?
That's how it happened.
Foi mais ou menos assim.
After some time, the first patient with the disease was discovered,
Pouco depois, foram identificados os primeiros casos da doença
and that same doctor gave her thorough medical treatment.
e aquele médico fez o tratamento direitinho.
The truth is that when a patient really did appear, I was surprised.
Na verdade, fiquei surpreso quando realmente apareceu um paciente.
Because it wasn't as if I completely believed Miss Bertia's story.
Não é como se eu acreditasse totalmente na história da Srta. Bertia...
But I learned a lot.
Mas eu também aprendi muito.
The fact that I had difficulty guiding the doctor...
Sobre não ter conseguido orientar o médico direito...
and the fact that I made Miss Bertia feel so anxious...
Ou o fato de ter deixado a Srta. Bertia preocupada.
might be the result of my bad habits.
Talvez seja um mau hábito meu.
When I theorize, I understand too easily.
"Se pensarmos bem, é fácil perceber".
And I seem to have a tendency to omit explanations.
Eu acabo simplificando muito a explicação.
J-Just a moment, please.
Espere um pouquinho, por favor!
So much of that seems strange.
Isso não faz sentido.
Your Highness, why would you do all of that?
Por que está fazendo tudo isso?
Why?
Por quê?
I have no intention of ignoring my fiancée when she appears so anxious.
Não pretendo ignorar minha noiva, que está preocupada.
B-But an eleven year old child could hardly do all of that!
Mas como uma criança de 11 anos fez isso?
I am the crown prince.
Eu sou o príncipe herdeiro, sabia?
I can use the palace library,
Posso usar a biblioteca do palácio e, se obtiver a permissão de meu pai,
it's possible for me to call on brilliant experts for help.
também é possível contar com a ajuda de especialistas qualificados.
R-Really?
É... É mesmo?
No, of course not!
De jeito nenhum.
For a normal crown prince, it would be impossible!
Seria impossível para um príncipe normal.
That's amazing, Zeno!
Que incrível, Zeno!
You're so far away, and yet I can hear the voice of your heart.
Mesmo estando longe, consigo ouvir sua mente.
Is it really possible for things to work out so conveniently?
Será que existe mesmo esse tipo de oportunismo?!
I suppose I should expect it from the genius known as the Android Prince.
Não é à toa que ele é conhecido como o Príncipe Androide!
Android?
Androide?
Please don't worry about the details.
Bem, não se preocupe com esses detalhes.
If your mother is safe and the harm to the people was kept to a minimum,
Se sua mãe está bem, e os danos causados à população foram mínimos,
then everything's fine, isn't it?
tudo bem assim.
Y-Yes, you're right!
É-É verdade!
After all, everyone has evaded the evil clutches of the epidemic.
Afinal, todos conseguiram escapar da doença contagiosa.
This is for the best!
É isso mesmo!
Yes. I see you've given up on thinking about it.
É, você desistiu de pensar.
Oh, that's right. Aside from the official gift,
É mesmo. Além do presente oficial,
I have something else I'd like to give you, Miss Bertia.
tenho algo para te entregar, Srta. Bertia.
You still have some other surprise for me?!
Ainda tem alguma surpresa?!
It's from me personally. A handmade birthday present.
É um presente de aniversário feito por mim.
The truth is that this is actually a universal antidote.
Na verdade, isso é um antídoto universal.
Wh-What?
O quê? Hã?
A universal antidote?
O quê? Um antídoto universal?
While I was researching all sorts of things,
Enquanto pesquisava sobre vários assuntos,
I found an interesting book in the palace library.
encontrei um livro interessante na biblioteca do palácio.
What's that?
O que será?
A seam?
Uma junta?
It moved.
Mexeu?
Using the knowledge I gained from there, I tried making that.
Eu tentei fazer com base no conhecimento que consegui ali.
Since you'll become my wife, it's possible that your life will be threatened.
Afinal, sua vida corre risco, já que será minha esposa.
I thought it could be a protective charm.
Pense que é seu amuleto.
Yes, it suits you very well.
É, fica muito bem em você!
Th-Thank you... very much.
Ah, muito obrigada.
Prince Cecil.
Príncipe Cecil!
I, Bertia Ibil Noches, swear upon this necklace!
Eu, Bertia Ibil Noches, juro por este colar!
In order to repay the debt of gratitude I owe you,
Retribuirei a gentileza que me demonstrou,
I will make sure to thoroughly rectify the scenario...
revisarei cuidadosamente o roteiro e...
and I will show you what a magnificent villainess I can become!
...vou mostrar a você o que é ser uma verdadeira vilã!
First, my father, who should have started down the path of evil...
Primeiro, meu pai. Ele deveria ter seguido o caminho do mal.
I'll have him turn into a proper villain!
Ele vai virar um vilão direitinho!
No, that's really all right.
Acho que não precisa. Seria um problema ficar sem o chanceler.
I will make sure that Your Highness and the heroine get your happy ending!
Vou assegurar que o seu final com a heroína seja feliz!
Yes. It seems she isn't listening to most of what I'm saying.
É. Parece que você quase não está ouvindo nada do que digo.
Well, that's all right. It does seem entertaining, after all.
Bom, tudo bem, parece interessante!
I'll give it my very best!
Vou dar o meu melhor!
Bertia has renewed her resolution.
Bertia renovou sua motivação
Translator: Timer: Editor: Quality Control: Final Quality Control:
\hLegendas brasileiras \hTradução Sayuri Tanamate \hEdição Vinícius Dias \hRevisão Lívia Machado \hProdução Gustavo Hoffmann
Are you injured?
Você está machucado?
It's all right. There's nothing to be scared of.
Tudo bem. Não precisa ter medo.
I remember...
Eu lembrei!
I am...
Eu...
Chapter 2 An Observation Log of the Self-Proclaimed Villainess's Debut into Society.
Episódio 02
"An Observation Log of the Self-Proclaimed Villainess's Debut into Society."
O Registro da Autoproclamada Vilã